<!-- This is used to install the plugin as an add-on: https://www.oxygenxml.com/doc/versions/19.1/ug-editor/topics/packing-and-deploying-addons.html#packing-and-deploying-addons -->
<xt:extensions xmlns:xt="http://www.oxygenxml.com/ns/extension"
    xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
    xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.oxygenxml.com/ns/extension http://www.oxygenxml.com/ns/extension/extensions.xsd">
    <xt:extension xmlns:xt="http://www.oxygenxml.com/ns/extension" id="com.oxygenxml.git">
        <xt:location
            href="https://github.com/oxygenxml/Oxygen-Git-Plugin/releases/download/${project.version}/${project.build.finalName}-plugin.jar"/>
        <xt:version>${project.version}</xt:version>
        <xt:oxy_version>21.1+</xt:oxy_version>
        <xt:type>plugin</xt:type>
        <xt:author>Syncro Soft</xt:author>
        <xt:name>Git Client</xt:name>
        <xt:description>
            <html xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
                <head>
                    <title>Git Client</title>
                    <style type="text/css"> ol {margin-top:0px;} p
                        {margin-top:0px;margin-bottom:5px;} </style>
                </head>
                <body>
                    <div>
                        <p>This add-on installs a Git client in Oxygen. It contributes multiple side-views,
				each one specialized in doing different Git operations, the main one being named <i>Git Staging</i>.
				Using the Git Client add-on, various Git operations can be performed, such as committing changes into the local repository, 
				pushing/pulling changes to/from the remote repository, creating, checking out and deleting branches,
				showing the history of the repository resources and more. The add-on also includes a tool for comparing and merging changes.
			</p>
                    </div>
		    <div>
                        <h3>What's new in version 2.5.0</h3>
                        <ol>
			    <li>Added a new field in the login dialog for authenticating using a personal access token. Note that from August 13, 2021, GitHub
				    will no longer accept password-based authentication (
				    <a href="https://github.blog/2020-12-15-token-authentication-requirements-for-git-operations">
					    https://github.blog/2020-12-15-token-authentication-requirements-for-git-operations
				    </a>).
			    </li>
			    <li>After a repository that contains submodules is cloned, all submodules are also automatically initialized and cloned.</li>
			    <li>When pulling the remote changes for a repository that contains submodules, the submodules are updated as well (by default).
				    This behavior depends on the <i>Update all submodules after pulling changes from the remote repository</i> option
				    from the <i>Git Client</i> preferences page in Oxygen.</li>
		            <li>If a submodule appears as changed in the <i>Unstaged files</i> area, you can open it 
				    using the <i>Open</i> action from the contextual menu.</li>
			    <li>The tooltip shown for a modified submodule from the <i>Ustanged files</i> area now presents information about 
				    the currently and previously tracked commits.</li>
		            <li>Branches created from other local branches are now automatically checked out. This behavior can be
				    disabled by deselecting the <i>Checkout branch</i> option in the <i>Create branch</i> dialog box.</li>
			    <li>The <i>Git Staging</i> side-view has been slightly redesigned and now has a cleaner look.</li>
			    <li>Added support for Dutch localization.</li>
			    <li>Fixed an issue where debugging the Git Client using Apapche Log4j did not work.</li>
			    <li>Fixed various other bugs and added several small UX improvements.</li>
                        </ol>
                    </div>
                    <div>
                        <h3>What's new in version 2.4.0</h3>
                        <ol>
                            <li>Added an "Abort merge" button for when conflicts result after a 
                            	<i>Pull (merge)</i> operation. It allows you to abort the current
                             	conflict resolution process.</li>
                            <li>Added a set of options in the Git Client preferences page that
                            	can be used to decide whether to always switch to a newly detected working copy
                            	from a project, to never switch, or to always ask.</li>
                            <li>Added a "Preferences" action in the Settings menu that acts as a shortcut
                            	to the Git Client preferences page.</li>
		            <li>Fixed an issue where pushing to a remote branch did not work when local and upstream branch had diffenrent names.</li>
                            <li>Integrated numerous other bug fixes, UI improvements, and speed improvements.</li>
			    <li>The JGit component included in the Git Client was updated to version 5.10.0.</li>
                        </ol>
                    </div>
                    <div>
                        <h3>What's new in version 2.3.1</h3>
                        <ol>
                            <li>Fixed some performance problems introduced by version 2.3.0.</li>
                            <li>Fixed an issue where branches removed from the remote repository were
                            still presented in the Git Branch Manager view even after refreshing it.</li>
                        </ol>
                    </div>
                    <div>
                        <h3>What's new in version 2.3.0</h3>
                        <ol>
                            <li>The Git Client now contributes a new side-view, called the <b>Git
                                    Branch Manager</b>, which presents all the local and remote
                                branches as a tree. Actions were added to the tree's contextual menu
                                to make it very easy to check out branches, and to create or delete
                                branches.</li>
                            <li>You can now easily switch between local branches using a drop-down
                                menu in the top-right corner of the Git Staging view or by using the
                                Git Branch Manager.</li>
                            <li>A new action (<b>Reset "[branch_name]" to this commit</b>) was added
                                in the history table that can be used to undo changes by moving the
                                HEAD of the current branch to the selected commit.</li>
                            <li>Some editor variables are now supported, including: <ul>
                                    <li>${git(working_copy_name)}</li>
                                    <li>${git(working_copy_path)}</li>
                                    <li>${git(short_branch_name)}</li>
                                    <li>${git(full_branch_name)}</li>
                                </ul>
                            </li>
                            <li>The Git History view now has better automatic refresh support.</li>
                            <li>A confirmation dialog box has been added for instances when you try
                                to commit without a message.</li>
                            <li>The add-on now contributes a preferences page (Options > Preferences
                                > Plugins > Git Client) that contains a "Notify me about new commits
                                in the remote repository" option. When this option is selected,
                                Oxygen will show notification messages when it detects that new
                                commits have been pushed to the remote repository.</li>
                            <li>Support for French localization was added.</li>
                            <li>The JGit component included in the Git Client was updated to version
                                5.9.0.</li>
                            <li>Various other minor improvements and bug fixes were
                                implemented.</li>
                        </ol>
                        <p>For more information about the add-on's features, see <a
                                href="https://github.com/oxygenxml/oxygen-git-plugin/blob/master/README.md"
                                >the README document</a>.</p>
                    </div>
                    <div>
                        <h3>What's new in version 2.2.0</h3>
                        <ol>
                            <li>Added the possibility to amend the last commit.</li>
                            <li>Added the possibility to automatically push changes to the remote
                                repository when committing.</li>
                            <li>Added the possibility to create a new branch starting from the
                                selected commit in the History table, by using the "Create branch"
                                contextual action.</li>
                            <li>Added the possibility to compare two revisions of the same file from
                                the Git History view, by using the "Compare with each other" action
                                in the contextual menu of the history table.</li>
                            <li>Added the possibility to reset the stored credentials, by using the
                                "Reset credentials" action in the Settings menu from the main
                                toolbar.</li>
                            <li>If you have a local branch that is not tracking a remote branch, the
                                push button tooltip suggests that you push to create a remote branch
                                with the same name as the local one.</li>
                            <li>Incoming and outgoing commits are marked in the history table with
                                corresponding arrow characters.</li>
                            <li>Improved local repository detection when selecting a project.</li>
                            <li>Updated JGit to version 5.7.0 (which, among other things, fixes
                                client-side hooks execution).</li>
                            <li>Fixed a bug where failing commits did not show any messages to the
                                user.</li>
                            <li>Fixed other small bugs.</li>
                        </ol>
                        <p>For more information about the add-on's features, see <a
                                href="https://github.com/oxygenxml/oxygen-git-plugin/blob/master/README.md"
                                >the README document</a>.</p>
                    </div>
                    <div>
                        <h3>What's new in version 2.1.1</h3>
                        <ol>
                            <li>Fixed a bug where the Text/Author page contextual menu was not shown
                                when the opened document was remote (e.g. from a WebDAV
                                server).</li>
                        </ol>
                    </div>
                    <div>
                        <h3>What's new in version 2.1.0</h3>
                        <ol>
                            <li>Updated the JGit library to version 5.6.</li>
                            <li>Added a "Clear history" action in the working copies combo box.</li>
                            <li>Added the "Show history" and "Show blame" actions to the contextual
                                menus of the resources from the Project view and of the Text and
                                Author editor pages.</li>
                            <li>Implemented renaming detection in the Git History view. Renamed
                                resources are presented using a suggestive icon (containing the "R"
                                letter). All the actions from the Git History view take into account
                                the entire history of a resource, including renames and path
                                changes.</li>
                            <li>Numerous bug fixes and small improvements.</li>
                        </ol>
                    </div>
                    <div>
                        <h3>What's new in version 2.0.0</h3>
                        <ol>
                            <li>Added a new <b>Git History</b> side-view, available from the toolbar
                                for the entire repository, or from the contextual menu for each
                                unstaged resource.</li>
                            <li>Added a <b>Show blame</b> action in the contextual menu of unstaged
                                resources. This action works in conjunction with the <b>Git
                                    History</b> side-view, where the revision highlighted in the
                                main editor is selected for presenting more details.</li>
                            <li>Added a <b>Pull (rebase)</b> action in the toolbar.</li>
                            <li>Added more 2X icons for high resolution screens.</li>
                            <li>Fixed UI freeze issues when working with large repositories.</li>
                            <li>Fixed some UI glitches such as unintended borders, lack of padding,
                                crowded components, etc.</li>
                            <li>Improved speed when performing various operations, such as
                                committing or changing the repository.</li>
                            <li>Other small bug fixes.</li>
                        </ol>
                    </div>
                    <div>
                        <h3>What's new in version 1.5.2</h3>
                        <ol>
                            <li>Updated to JGit version 5.4.2 which comes with various bug fixes: <a
                                    href="https://projects.eclipse.org/projects/technology.jgit/releases/5.4.2/review"
                                    >https://projects.eclipse.org/projects/technology.jgit/releases/5.4.2/review</a></li>
                            <li>Fixed issue: Oxygen freezes on start-up.</li>
                            <li>Fixed issue: Opening a Git repository fails with a
                                java.lang.NullPointerException.</li>
                        </ol>
                    </div>
                    <div>
                        <h3>What's new in version 1.5.1</h3>
                        <ol>
                            <li>Updated to JGit 5.4.0.</li>
                            <li>Fixed issue: switching between flat mode and tree mode didn't always
                                work.</li>
                            <li>Fixed issue: authentication through SSH using a passphase was broken
                                in the previous build.</li>
                            <li>Other bug fixes</li>
                        </ol>
                    </div>
                    <div>
                        <h3>What's new in version 1.5.0</h3>
                        <ol>
                            <li>Updated to JGit 5.3.1.</li>
                            <li>The add-on now works with more kinds of SSH keys, by using JGit's
                                new SSH session factory based on 'Apache MINA sshd' by default. See
                                    <a href="https://wiki.eclipse.org/JGit/New_and_Noteworthy/5.2"
                                    >https://wiki.eclipse.org/JGit/New_and_Noteworthy/5.2</a> for a
                                full list of benefits.</li>
                            <!-- <li>The add-on now allows comparing images.</li> -->
                            <li>The tooltips of the push/pull buttons and the branch label now also
                                present the remote repository.</li>
                            <li>Bug fixes</li>
                            <li>Speed improvements</li>
                        </ol>
                    </div>
                    <div>
                        <h3>What's new in version 1.4.0</h3>
                        <ol>
                            <li>Update to JGit 5.2.1.</li>
                            <li>Performance improvements when checking the status of the
                                repository.</li>
                            <li>Fixed bug that led to file loss when changing the letter case in a
                                file name.</li>
                            <li>Better error message when the working copy is locked.</li>
                            <li>When closing, Oxygen will wait for Git commands to complete to avoid
                                possible side effects such as leaving the worky copy locked.</li>
                        </ol>
                    </div>
                    <div>
                        <h3>What's new in version 1.3.2</h3>
                        <ol>
                            <li>Initalize and update submodules if needed when the user opens a
                                submodule.</li>
                        </ol>
                    </div>
                    <div>
                        <h3>What's new in version 1.3.1</h3>
                        <ol>
                            <li>Present an error message when Pull fails because local changes would
                                be overwritten by merge.</li>
                        </ol>
                    </div>
                    <div>
                        <h3>What's new in version 1.2.11</h3>
                        <ol>
                            <li>Various performance optimizations, bug fixes and the ability to
                                check out a specific branch when cloning a repository.</li>
                        </ol>
                    </div>
                    <div>
                        <h3>What's new in version 1.2.10</h3>
                        <ol>
                            <li>Speed improvement when invoking the contextual menu the Project
                                view.</li>
                        </ol>
                    </div>
                    <div>
                        <h3>What's new in version 1.2.9</h3>
                        <ol>
                            <li>Fixed various issues encountered while working with resources in the
                                tree view.</li>
                        </ol>
                    </div>
                    <div>
                        <h3>What's new in version 1.2.6</h3>
                        <ol>
                            <li>Bug fix: The contextual menu didn't show when running Oxygen on Mac
                                OS X (broken in version 1.2.5)</li>
                            <li>Improved the calculation of pull behind and push ahead counters</li>
                        </ol>
                    </div>
                    <div>
                        <h3>What's new in version 1.2.5</h3>
                        <ol>
                            <li>Bug fixes </li>
                            <li>Performance improvements</li>
                        </ol>
                    </div>
                    <div>
                        <h1>Using the plugin</h1>
                        <p><b>Note:</b> After installing the plugin, if the <b>Git Staging</b> view
                            is not visible, you can open it from the <b>Window > Show View</b>
                            menu.</p>
                        <p>For information about how to use the Git Client, please see the README
                            document on GitHub: <a
                                href="https://github.com/oxygenxml/oxygen-git-plugin/blob/master/README.md"
                                >
                                https://github.com/oxygenxml/oxygen-git-plugin/blob/master/README.md</a>.</p>
                    </div>
                </body>
            </html>
        </xt:description>
        <xt:license><![CDATA[
		Copyright 2018 Syncro Soft SRL

Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
You may obtain a copy of the License at

    http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0

Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
limitations under the License.

This plugin may include certain of the following third party software components.
The license terms applicable to such third party software components are listed below:

commons-codec-1.6
Site: http://commons.apache.org/codec/
License: Apache License 2.0 ( http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0)

commons-logging-1.1.3
Site: http://commons.apache.org/proper/commons-logging/
License: Apache License 2.0 ( http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0)

httpclient-4.3.6
Site: http://hc.apache.org/httpcomponents-client     
License: Apache License 2.0 ( http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0)

httpcore-4.3.3
Site: http://hc.apache.org/httpcomponents-core-ga
License: Apache License 2.0 ( http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0)

log4j-1.2.14
Site: http://logging.apache.org/log4j/docs/
License: Apache License 2.0 ( http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0)

JavaEWAH-1.1.6
Site: https://github.com/lemire/javaewah
License: Apache License 2.0 ( http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0)

jsch-0.1.54
Site: http://www.jcraft.com/jsch
License: BSD-style license, see below:
"Copyright (c) 2002-2015 Atsuhiko Yamanaka, JCraft,Inc.
All rights reserved.

Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without
modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions are met:

  1. Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright notice,
     this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.

  2. Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright
     notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer in
     the documentation and/or other materials provided with the distribution.

  3. The names of the authors may not be used to endorse or promote products
     derived from this software without specific prior written permission.

THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED ``AS IS'' AND ANY EXPRESSED OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES,
INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND
FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL JCRAFT,
INC. OR ANY CONTRIBUTORS TO THIS SOFTWARE BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT,
INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT
LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES; LOSS OF USE, DATA,
OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF
LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING
NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS SOFTWARE,
EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE."

org.eclipse.jgit-4.9.2.201712150930-r,
Eclipse Distribution License - v 1.0

Copyright (c) 2007, Eclipse Foundation, Inc. and its licensors.

All rights reserved.

Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions are met:

    Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.
    Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer in the documentation and/or other materials provided with the distribution.
    Neither the name of the Eclipse Foundation, Inc. nor the names of its contributors may be used to endorse or promote products derived from this software without specific prior written permission. 

THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE COPYRIGHT HOLDERS AND CONTRIBUTORS "AS IS" AND ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE COPYRIGHT OWNER OR CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES; LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.

SHA-1 UbcCheck - MIT

Copyright (c) 2017:

                Marc Stevens
                Cryptology Group
                Centrum Wiskunde & Informatica
                P.O. Box 94079, 1090 GB Amsterdam, Netherlands
                marc@marc-stevens.nl
            

                Dan Shumow
                Microsoft Research
                danshu@microsoft.com
            

Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy of this software and associated documentation files (the "Software"), to deal in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:

    The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in all copies or substantial portions of the Software.

THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM, OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE SOFTWARE.

slf4j-api-1.7.2
Site: http://www.slf4j.org
License: MIT license, see below: "
Copyright (c) 2004-2017 QOS.ch All rights reserved.
Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy of this software and associated documentation files (the "Software"), to deal in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:
The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in all copies or substantial portions of the Software.
THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM, OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE SOFTWARE."

slf4j-log4j12-1.7.25
Site: http://www.slf4j.org
License: MIT license, see below: "
Copyright (c) 2004-2017 QOS.ch All rights reserved.
Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy of this software and associated documentation files (the "Software"), to deal in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:
The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in all copies or substantial portions of the Software.
THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM, OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE SOFTWARE."
]]></xt:license>
    </xt:extension>
</xt:extensions>
