<!-- This is used to install the plugin as an add-on: https://www.oxygenxml.com/doc/versions/18.1/ug-editor/topics/packing-and-deploying-addons.html#packing-and-deploying-addons -->
<xt:extensions xmlns:xt="http://www.oxygenxml.com/ns/extension"
	xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
	xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.oxygenxml.com/ns/extension http://www.oxygenxml.com/ns/extension/extensions.xsd">
	<xt:extension xmlns:xt="http://www.oxygenxml.com/ns/extension"
		id="com.oxygenxml.git">
		<xt:location href="https://github.com/oxygenxml/Oxygen-Git-Plugin/releases/download/${project.version}/${project.build.finalName}-plugin.jar" />
		<xt:version>${project.version}</xt:version> 
		<xt:oxy_version>18.1+</xt:oxy_version>
		<xt:type>plugin</xt:type>
		<xt:author>Syncro Soft</xt:author>
		<xt:name>Git Support</xt:name>
		<xt:description>
		   <html xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
		      <head>
		         <title>Git support plugin</title>
		         <style type="text/css">
		            ol {margin-top:0px;}
		            p {margin-top:0px;margin-bottom:5px;}
		         </style>
		      </head>
		      <body>
		          <div>
		              <p>This add-on contributes a built-in Git client directly into Oxygen in the form of a <b>Git Staging</b> view that includes various actions that perform common Git commands, such as push, pull, change branch, commit, and more. It also includes a built-in tool for comparing and merging changes.</p>
		          </div>
		          <div>
		              <h3>What's new in version 1.3.2</h3>
		              <ol>
		                  <li>Initalize and update submodules if needed when the user opens a submodule.</li>
		              </ol>
		          </div>
		          <div>
		              <h3>What's new in version 1.3.1</h3>
		              <ol>
		                  <li>Present an error message when Pull fails because local changes would be overwritten by merge.</li>
		              </ol>
		          </div>
		          <div>
		              <h3>What's new in version 1.2.11</h3>
		              <ol>
		                  <li>Various performance optimizations, bug fixes and the ability to check out a specific branch when cloning a repository.</li>
		              </ol>
		          </div>
		        <div>
		          <h3>What's new in version 1.2.10</h3>
		          <ol>
		            <li>Speed improvement when invoking the contextual menu the Project view.</li>
		          </ol>
		        </div>
		      	<div>
		      		<h3>What's new in version 1.2.9</h3>
		      		<ol>
		      			<li>Fixed various issues encountered while working with resources in the tree view.</li>
		      		</ol>
		      	</div>
		         <div>
		            <h3>What's new in version 1.2.6</h3>
		            <ol>
		               <li>Bug fix: The contextual menu didn't show when running Oxygen on Mac OS X (broken in version 1.2.5)</li>
		               <li>Improved the calculation of pull behind and push ahead counters</li>
		            </ol>
		         </div>
		         <div>
		            <h3>What's new in version 1.2.5</h3>
		            <ol>
		               <li>Bug fixes </li>
		               <li>Performance improvements</li>
		            </ol>
		         </div>
		         <div>
		            <h1>Using the plugin</h1>
		            <p><b>Note:</b> After installing the plugin, if the <b>Git Staging</b> view is not
		               visible, you can open it from the <b>Window > Show View</b> menu.</p>
		            
		            <h2>Selecting the working copy</h2>
		            <div><p>Click the <b>Browse</b> button to select a working copy from your file system. The selected
		               folder must be a Git Repository. You can also clone a new repository using a
		               toolbar action.</p>
		            </div>
		            
		            <h2>Unstaged resources area</h2>
		            <div>
		               <p>In the unstaged resources area (the one on top) you will see all the modifications that have occurred since
		                  your last commit (files that have been modified, new files and deleted files). Various actions are available
		                  in the contextual menu (<b>Open</b>, <b>Open in compare editor</b>).</p>
		               <p>You can stage all the files by clicking the <b>Stage All</b> button or you can stage some of them
		                  by selecting and clicking the <b>Stage Selected</b> button. You can even individually stage each file 
		                  by clicking the <b>Stage</b> button that appears next to each file.</p>
		               <p>You can switch from the flat(table) view to a tree view
		                  by clicking on the button positioned above area.</p>
		            </div>
		            
		            <h2>Staged resources area</h2>
		            <div>
		               <p>In the staging area you will see all the resources that are ready to be committed. Any files from this area
		                  can be unstaged and sent back to the unstaged resources area. The staging area has similar actions with the unstaging area.</p>
		            </div>
		            
		            <h2>Comparing changes and conflict resolution</h2>
		            <div>
		               <p>At any time, if you want to see the differences between the
		                  last commit and your current modifications you can double click
		                  the file that appears either in the staging or unstaging area and the <a href="https://www.oxygenxml.com/doc/versions/19.0/ug-editor/topics/file-comparison-x-tools.html">Oxygen's Diff</a> window will 
		                  appear and highlight the changes.</p>
		               <p>If the file is in conflict (has been modified both by you and another), <a href="https://www.oxygenxml.com/doc/versions/19.0/ug-editor/topics/file-comparison-x-tools.html#file-comparison__threeway_comparisons">Oxygen's Three Way Diff</a>
		                  will show a comparison between the local change, the remote change, and the original base revision.</p>
		            </div>
		            
		            <h2>Committing</h2>
		            <div><p>After staging the files, on the bottom of the view you can input the commit message and commit them into your local repository.
		               For convenience, you can also select one of the previously entered messages.</p>
		            </div>
		            
		            <h2>Push/Pull</h2>
		            <div><p>To push your local repository changes to the remote one you must click on the <b>Push</b> button from the view's toolbar.
		               To bring the changes from the remote repository into your local one you must click on the <b>Pull</b> button from the same toolbar.</p></div>
		            
		         </div>
		      </body>
		   </html>
		</xt:description>
		<xt:license><![CDATA[
		Copyright 2018 Syncro Soft SRL

Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
You may obtain a copy of the License at

    http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0

Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
limitations under the License.

This plugin may include certain of the following third party software components.
The license terms applicable to such third party software components are listed below:

commons-codec-1.6
Site: http://commons.apache.org/codec/
License: Apache License 2.0 ( http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0)

commons-logging-1.1.3
Site: http://commons.apache.org/proper/commons-logging/
License: Apache License 2.0 ( http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0)

httpclient-4.3.6
Site: http://hc.apache.org/httpcomponents-client     
License: Apache License 2.0 ( http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0)

httpcore-4.3.3
Site: http://hc.apache.org/httpcomponents-core-ga
License: Apache License 2.0 ( http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0)

log4j-1.2.14
Site: http://logging.apache.org/log4j/docs/
License: Apache License 2.0 ( http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0)

JavaEWAH-1.1.6
Site: https://github.com/lemire/javaewah
License: Apache License 2.0 ( http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0)

jsch-0.1.54
Site: http://www.jcraft.com/jsch
License: BSD-style license, see below:
"Copyright (c) 2002-2015 Atsuhiko Yamanaka, JCraft,Inc.
All rights reserved.

Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without
modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions are met:

  1. Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright notice,
     this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.

  2. Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright
     notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer in
     the documentation and/or other materials provided with the distribution.

  3. The names of the authors may not be used to endorse or promote products
     derived from this software without specific prior written permission.

THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED ``AS IS'' AND ANY EXPRESSED OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES,
INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND
FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL JCRAFT,
INC. OR ANY CONTRIBUTORS TO THIS SOFTWARE BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT,
INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT
LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES; LOSS OF USE, DATA,
OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF
LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING
NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS SOFTWARE,
EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE."

org.eclipse.jgit-4.9.2.201712150930-r,
Eclipse Distribution License - v 1.0

Copyright (c) 2007, Eclipse Foundation, Inc. and its licensors.

All rights reserved.

Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions are met:

    Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.
    Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer in the documentation and/or other materials provided with the distribution.
    Neither the name of the Eclipse Foundation, Inc. nor the names of its contributors may be used to endorse or promote products derived from this software without specific prior written permission. 

THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE COPYRIGHT HOLDERS AND CONTRIBUTORS "AS IS" AND ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE COPYRIGHT OWNER OR CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES; LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.

SHA-1 UbcCheck - MIT

Copyright (c) 2017:

                Marc Stevens
                Cryptology Group
                Centrum Wiskunde & Informatica
                P.O. Box 94079, 1090 GB Amsterdam, Netherlands
                marc@marc-stevens.nl
            

                Dan Shumow
                Microsoft Research
                danshu@microsoft.com
            

Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy of this software and associated documentation files (the "Software"), to deal in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:

    The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in all copies or substantial portions of the Software.

THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM, OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE SOFTWARE.

slf4j-api-1.7.2
Site: http://www.slf4j.org
License: MIT license, see below: "
Copyright (c) 2004-2017 QOS.ch All rights reserved.
Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy of this software and associated documentation files (the "Software"), to deal in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:
The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in all copies or substantial portions of the Software.
THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM, OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE SOFTWARE."

slf4j-log4j12-1.7.25
Site: http://www.slf4j.org
License: MIT license, see below: "
Copyright (c) 2004-2017 QOS.ch All rights reserved.
Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy of this software and associated documentation files (the "Software"), to deal in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:
The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in all copies or substantial portions of the Software.
THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM, OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE SOFTWARE."
]]></xt:license>
	</xt:extension>
</xt:extensions>


