<!-- This is used to install the plugin as an add-on: https://www.oxygenxml.com/doc/versions/18.1/ug-editor/topics/packing-and-deploying-addons.html#packing-and-deploying-addons -->
<xt:extensions xmlns:xt="http://www.oxygenxml.com/ns/extension"
	xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
	xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.oxygenxml.com/ns/extension http://www.oxygenxml.com/ns/extension/extensions.xsd">
	<xt:extension xmlns:xt="http://www.oxygenxml.com/ns/extension"
		id="com.oxygenxml.git">
		<xt:location href="https://github.com/oxygenxml/Oxygen-Git-Plugin/releases/download/${project.version}/${project.build.finalName}-plugin.jar" />
		<xt:version>${project.version}</xt:version> 
		<xt:oxy_version>18.1+</xt:oxy_version>
		<xt:type>plugin</xt:type>
		<xt:author>Syncro Soft SRL</xt:author>
		<xt:name>Git Support (Experimental)</xt:name>
		<xt:description>
		   <html xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
		      <head>
		         <title>Git support plugin</title>
		         <style type="text/css">
		            ol {margin-top:0px;}
		            p {margin-top:0px;margin-bottom:5px;}
		         </style>
		      </head>
		      <body>
		         <div>
		            <h3>What's new in version 1.2.6</h3>
		            <ol>
		               <li>Bug fix: The contextual menu didn't show when running Oxygen on Mac OS X (broken in version 1.2.5)</li>
		               <li>Improved the calculation of pull behind and push ahead counters</li>
		            </ol>
		         </div>
		         <div>
		            <h3>What's new in version 1.2.5</h3>
		            <ol>
		               <li>Bug fixes </li>
		               <li>Performance improvements</li>
		            </ol>
		         </div>
		         <div>
		            <h1>Using the plugin</h1>
		            <p><b>Note:</b> After installing the plugin, if the <b>Git Staging</b> view is not
		               visible, you can open it from the <b>Window > Show View</b> menu.</p>
		            
		            <h2>Selecting the working copy</h2>
		            <div><p>Click the <b>Browse</b> button to select a working copy from your file system. The selected
		               folder must be a Git Repository. You can also clone a new repository using a
		               toolbar action.</p>
		            </div>
		            
		            <h2>Unstaged resources area</h2>
		            <div>
		               <p>In the unstaged resources area (the one on top) you will see all the modifications that have occurred since
		                  your last commit (files that have been modified, new files and deleted files). Various actions are available
		                  in the contextual menu (<b>Open</b>, <b>Open in compare editor</b>).</p>
		               <p>You can stage all the files by clicking the <b>Stage All</b> button or you can stage some of them
		                  by selecting and clicking the <b>Stage Selected</b> button. You can even individually stage each file 
		                  by clicking the <b>Stage</b> button that appears next to each file.</p>
		               <p>You can switch from the flat(table) view to a tree view
		                  by clicking on the button positioned above area.</p>
		            </div>
		            
		            <h2>Staged resources area</h2>
		            <div>
		               <p>In the staging area you will see all the resources that are ready to be committed. Any files from this area
		                  can be unstaged and sent back to the unstaged resources area. The staging area has similar actions with the unstaging area.</p>
		            </div>
		            
		            <h2>Comparing changes and conflict resolution</h2>
		            <div>
		               <p>At any time, if you want to see the differences between the
		                  last commit and your current modifications you can double click
		                  the file that appears either in the staging or unstaging area and the <a href="https://www.oxygenxml.com/doc/versions/19.0/ug-editor/topics/file-comparison-x-tools.html">Oxygen's Diff</a> window will 
		                  appear and highlight the changes.</p>
		               <p>If the file is in conflict (has been modified both by you and another), <a href="https://www.oxygenxml.com/doc/versions/19.0/ug-editor/topics/file-comparison-x-tools.html#file-comparison__threeway_comparisons">Oxygen's Three Way Diff</a>
		                  will show a comparison between the local change, the remote change, and the original base revision.</p>
		            </div>
		            
		            <h2>Committing</h2>
		            <div><p>After staging the files, on the bottom of the view you can input the commit message and commit them into your local repository.
		               For convenience, you can also select one of the previously entered messages.</p>
		            </div>
		            
		            <h2>Push/Pull</h2>
		            <div><p>To push your local repository changes to the remote one you must click on the <b>Push</b> button from the view's toolbar.
		               To bring the changes from the remote repository into your local one you must click on the <b>Pull</b> button from the same toolbar.</p></div>
		            
		         </div>
		      </body>
		   </html>
		</xt:description>
		<xt:license><![CDATA[
		Copyright 2018 Syncro Soft SRL

   Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
   you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
   You may obtain a copy of the License at

       http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0

   Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
   distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
   WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
   See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
   limitations under the License.
]]></xt:license>
	</xt:extension>
</xt:extensions>


