<!-- This is used to install the plugin as an add-on: https://www.oxygenxml.com/doc/versions/18.1/ug-editor/topics/packing-and-deploying-addons.html#packing-and-deploying-addons -->
<xt:extensions xmlns:xt="http://www.oxygenxml.com/ns/extension"
	xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
	xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.oxygenxml.com/ns/extension http://www.oxygenxml.com/ns/extension/extensions.xsd">
	<xt:extension xmlns:xt="http://www.oxygenxml.com/ns/extension"
		id="com.oxygenxml.git">
		<xt:location href="${project.build.finalName}-plugin.jar" />
		<xt:version>${project.version}</xt:version>
		<xt:oxy_version>17.0+</xt:oxy_version>
		<xt:type>plugin</xt:type>
		<xt:author>Oxygen XML Editor</xt:author>
		<xt:name>Git Support</xt:name>
		<xt:description>
			<html xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
				<head>
					<title>Git support plugin</title>
				</head>
				<body>
					<div>
						<p>After installing the plugin if the git window is not visible
							you should go to the "Window" menu -> show view -> Git Staging.
						</p>
						<p>Usage:
							- Select a working copy from your file system. The folder
							selected must be a git Repository otherwise the plugin will prompt
							you with an error message. The plugin assumes you already have a
							checkout repository.
							- After you have selected the repository the
							plugin will show you all the modification that have occurred since
							your last commit in the unstaging area (files that have been
							modified, new files and deleted files) with their location
							relative from the working copy and a button to individually stage
							them.
							- You then can then select to stage all those files by
							clicking on the "Stage All" button or some of them by selecting
							the files you want and clicking on the "Stage Selected" button or
							you can individually send a file to the staging area by clicking
							the "Stage" button that appears on the right for each file.
							- If you don't like the flat(table) view you can opt for a tree view
							by clicking on the button positioned above the table to the
							right. It has the same functionality
							- Once the files are in the
							staging area they are ready to be commited. But if you change
							your mind regarding one of the files that you previously staged
							you can of course unstage that file or all of them and commit
							only the files you want. Basically the staging area works the
							same as the unstaging area. Same buttons with the same
							functionality.
							- If you want to see the difference between the
							last commit and your current modifications you can double click
							the file that appears in the staging or unstaging area and a diff
							window will appear highlighting the changes.
							- Once you are
							satisfied with your file choice you can add a commit message in
							the text area and click on the commit button. The files will be
							commited locally on your system. To send them to the remote
							repository you must click on the push button(is the first button
							on the top left corner, represented by an "up arrow"). Ofcourse if
							you have changes that you want to bring from the remote
							repository you have the option to "pull" them using the second
							button located also in the top left corner represented by a "down
							arrow".
						</p>
					</div>
				</body>
			</html>
		</xt:description>
		<xt:license><![CDATA[(c) Syncro Soft , All rights reserved.
This Plug-In is part of the Oxygen XML Software and, as such, is part of the License Agreement governing the Oxygen XML Software.
]]></xt:license>
	</xt:extension>
</xt:extensions>


